Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection
Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection
- Marvel Comics
  - Contents of Box 253: (Box 253)
    - Title from indicia: Peter Parker: Spider Man Annual, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Peter Porker, The Spectacular Spider-Ham, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Popples, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Power Man and Iron Fist, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Power Pack, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Psi-Force, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Punisher, Issues from: 1980s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: The Punisher Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Punisher War Journal, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Quasar, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Rogue, Issues from: 2000s
  - Contents of Box 254: (Box 254)
    - Title from indicia: Saga of the Sub-Mariner, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Sectaurs, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Sectaurs: Warriors of the Symbion
    - Title from indicia: The Sensational She-Hulk, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Sergio Aragonés Groo the Wanderer, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Shadowmasters, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Silver Hawks, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Silver Surfer, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Silver Surfer Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Solo Avengers, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Solo Avengers starring Hawkeye and Moon Knight
      - Cover Title: Solo Avengers starring Hawkeye and Scarlet Witch
      - Cover Title: Solo Avengers starring Hawkeye and Falcon
      - Cover Title: Solo Avengers starring Hawkeye and Doctor Druid
    - Title from indicia: Special Missions, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: G. I. Joe Special Missions
    - Title from indicia: The Spectacular Spider-Man, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Speedball, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Speedball: The Masked Marvel
    - Title from indicia: Spellbound, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Girl, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man versus Wolverine, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man's Tangled Web, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Spitfire and the Troubleshooters, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Star Brand, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Star Wars, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Startling Stories: Banner, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Strange Tales, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Strange Tales featuring Cloak and Dagger and Doctor Strange
      - Cover Title: Strange Tales featuring Dagger and Doctor Strange
    - Title from indicia: Strikeforce: Morituri, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Thor, Issues from: 1980s,2000s
      - Cover Title: The Mighty Thor
    - Title from indicia: Thor: Godstorm, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Thunderbolts, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Thundercats, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Top Dog, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Transformers, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Transformers: Head Masters, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Transformers: The Movie, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Transformers Universe, Issues from: 1980s
  - Contents of Box 255: (Box 255)
    - Title from indicia: Ultimate Marvel Team-Up, Issues from: 2000s
      - Cover Title: Ultimate Marvel Team-Up: Spider-Man and The Punisher and Daredevil
      - Cover Title: Ultimate Marvel Team-Up: Spider-Man and the Fantastic Four
      - Cover Title: Ultimate Marvel Team-Up: Spider-Man and the Man-Thing
      - Cover Title: Ultimate Marvel Team-Up: Spider-Man and the X-Men
      - Cover Title: Ultimate Marvel Team-Up: Spider-Man and Doctor Strange
    - Title from indicia: Ultimate Spider-Man, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Ultimate X-Men, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: The Uncanny X-Men, Issues from: 1980s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Uncanny X-Men 2001, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: U. S. War Machine, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: The Vision and Scarlet Witch, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Visionaries, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Visionaries: Knights of the Magical Light
    - Title from indicia: The War, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Web of Spider-Man, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Web of Spider-Man Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: West Coast Avengers, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: West Coast Avengers Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: What if...?, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: What if the Alien Costume had Possessed Spider-Man?
      - Cover Title: What if the Vision had Destroyed the Avengers?
      - Cover Title: What if the X-Men Lost to Inferno?
    - Title from indicia: Wolfpack, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Wolverine, Issues from: 1980s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Wolverine 2001, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Wolverine: The Origin, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: X-Factor, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: X-Factor Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: X-Force, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men: Evolution, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men Unlimited, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men versus the Avengers, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: X-treme X-Men, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: X-treme X-Men 2001, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: X-treme X-Men: Savageland, Issues from: 2000s
  - Contents of Box 256: (Box 256)
    - Title from indicia: Alpha Flight, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Alpha Flight Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Amazing Spider-Man, Issues from: 1980s,1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Amazing Spider-Man 1999, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: A-Next, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Avataars: Covenant of the Shield, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: The Avengers, Issues from: 1980s,1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Avengers 1999, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Avengers: Celestial Quest, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Avengers: Forever, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Avengers Infinity, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Before the FF: The Storms, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Before the FF: Reed Richards, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Bishop The Last X-Man, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Black Goliath, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Black Panther, Issues from: 1980s,1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Black Sun: X-Men, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Black Widow, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Bullwinkle and Rocky, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Cable, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Captain America, Issues from: 1980s,1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Captain America 2000, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Captain America: Sentinel of Liberty, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Captain Marvel, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Classic X-Men, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Conan Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Conan the Barbarian, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Conan: Flame and the Fiend, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Conan the King, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Contest of Champions II, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Daredevil, Issues from: 1980s,1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Daredevil: Ninja, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Darkdevil, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Deadpool, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
      - Cover Title: Deadpool: Agent of Weapon X
    - Title from indicia: Deathlok, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Doc Savage, Issues from: 1970s
  - Contents of Box 257: (Box 257)
    - Title from indicia: Doctor Strange, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Doom, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: D. P. 7, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Earth X, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Elfquest, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Eternals, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Exiles, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Fantastic Four, Issues from: 1980s,1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Fantastic Four: 1 2 3 4, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: The Flintstone Kids, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: 4th, Issues from: 2000s
      - Cover Title: A Universe X Special
    - Title from indicia: Galactus the Devourer, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Gambit, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Gambit 1999, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Gambit 2000, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Generation X, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: G. I. Joe A Real American Hero, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: G. I. Joe Special Missions, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: G. I. Joe Yearbook, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Heathcliff, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Hellcat, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Hulk, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Hulk 2000, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: The Incredible Hulk, Issues from: 1970s
  - Contents of Box 258: (Box 258)
    - Title from indicia: The Incredible Hulk, Issues from: 1980s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Incredible Hulk versus Superman, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Inhumans, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Iron Fist: Wolverine, Issues from: 2000s
      - Cover Title: Iron Fist/Wolverine: The Return of K'un Lun
    - Title from indicia: Iron Man, Issues from: 1980s,1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Iron Man 1999, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Iron Man 2000, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Iron Man Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Iron Man: Bad Blood, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: J 2, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Justice, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Madballs, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Magik, Issues from: 2000s
      - Cover Title: X-Men: Magik
    - Title from indicia: Magneto Rex, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Boy, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Fanfare, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Marvel: The Lost Generation, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Knights, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: The Marvel Saga: The Official History of the Marvel Universe, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Masters of the Universe, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Maximum Security, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Maximum Security: Dangerous Planet, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Moon Knight, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Muppet Babies, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Jim Henson's Muppet Babies
    - Title from indicia: Mutant X, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: The 'Nam, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The New Mutants, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: New X-Men, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Nick Fury vs. S.H.I.E.L.D., Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Nova, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Nova: The Human Rocket
  - Contents of Box 259: (Box 259)
    - Title from indicia: The Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: The Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe Deluxe Edition
      - Cover Title: The Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe Book of the Dead Deluxe Edition
    - Title from indicia: The Official Marvel Index to the Avengers, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Official Marvel Index to the X-Men, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Peter Parker, the Spectacular Spider-Man, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Peter Parker: Spider-Man, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Peter Parker: Spider-Man 1999, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Peter Parker: Spider-Man 2000, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Power Pack, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Psi-Force, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Punisher, Issues from: 1980s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Red Sonja, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Rom, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Savage She-Hulk, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Sentry, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Sergio Aragonés Groo the Wanderer, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Sgt. Fury, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Sgt. Fury and his Howling Commandos
    - Title from indicia: Sgt. Fury and his Howling Commandos, Issues from: 1970s
  - Contents of Box 260: (Box 260)
    - Title from indicia: Sgt. Fury and his Howling Commandos, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
    - Title from indicia: Silver Hawks, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Silver Surfer, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Skull, the Slayer, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Slingers, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Solo Avengers, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Solo Avengers starring Hawkeye and Mockingbird
      - Cover Title: Solo Avengers starring Hawkeye and Black Knight
      - Cover Title: Solo Avengers starring Hawkeye and Black Widow
      - Cover Title: Solo Avengers starring Hawkeye and Doctor Pym
    - Title from indicia: Space Knights, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: The Spectacular Spider-Man, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Spellbound, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Girl, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man: Chapter One, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man: Death and Destiny, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man: Revenge of the Green Goblin, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Man's Tangled Web, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Spider-Woman, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Squadron Supreme, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Star Brand, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Startling Stories: Banner, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Star Wars, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Strange Tales, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Strange Tales featuring Cloak and Dazzler and Doctor Strange
      - Cover Title: Strange Tales featuring Cloak and Dagger and Doctor Strange
    - Title from indicia: Strikeforce: Morituri, Issues from: 1980s
  - Contents of Box 261: (Box 261)
    - Title from indicia: Thor, Issues from: 1980s,1990s,2000s
      - Cover Title: The Mighty Thor
    - Title from indicia: Thor: Godstorm, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Thunderbolts, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Thundercats, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Transformers, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Transformers: Head Masters, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Ultimate Spider-Man, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: The Uncanny X-Men, Issues from: 1980s,1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Universe X, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Universe X: X, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: U. S. War Machine, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: The Vision and the Scarlet Witch, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Visionaries, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Visionaries: Knights of the Magical Light
    - Title from indicia: Web of Spider-Man, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Webspinners: Tales of Spider-Man, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: West Coast Avengers, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: What if...? Special, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: What if Iron Man had been a Traitor?
    - Title from indicia: Wolverine, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Wolverine/Punisher Revelation, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Factor, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: X-51, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Force, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: X-Man, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men 1999, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men: Children of the Atom, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men: Declassified, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men The Hidden Years, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men: The Search for Cyclops, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men True Friends, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-Men Unlimited, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-treme X-Men: Savage Land, Issues from: 2000s
  - Contents of Box 262: (Box 262)
    - Title from indicia: Battlestar Galactica, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
    - Title from indicia: Black Panther, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Captain America, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Champions, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Conan Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Creatures on the Loose, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Doctor Strange, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
  - Contents of Box 263: (Box 263)
    - Title from indicia: Fear, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Adventure into Fear with the Man Thing
      - Cover Title: Adventure into Fear with the Man Called Morbius, the Living Vampire
    - Title from indicia: The Human Fly, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Incredible Hulk, Issues from: 1960s,1970s,1980s
  - Contents of Box 264: (Box 264)
    - Title from indicia: The Incredible Hulk, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Iron Fist, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Iron Man, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Man from Atlantis, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Fanfare, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Feature, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Marvel Feature presents Red Sonja
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Spotlight, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Marvel Spotlight on Red Wolf
      - Cover Title: Marvel Spotlight on Werewolf by Night
      - Cover Title: Marvel Spotlight on Ghost Rider
      - Cover Title: Marvel Spotlight on The Son of Satan
      - Cover Title: Marvel Spotlight on The Seventh Voyage of Sinbad
      - Cover Title: Marvel Spotlight on The Scarecrow
      - Cover Title: Marvel Spotlight on Sub-Mariner
      - Cover Title: Marvel Spotlight on The Moon Knight
      - Cover Title: Marvel Spotlight on the Warriors Three
      - Cover Title: Marvel Spotlight on Nick Fury, Agent of SHIELD
      - Cover Title: Marvel Spotlight on The Spider-Woman
      - Cover Title: Marvel Spotlight on Deathlok the Demolisher
  - Contents of Box 265: (Box 265)
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Team-Up, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
      Note: This series contains a new cover title on each issue which pairs Spider-Man with another Marvel character. Cover titles not listed here.
    - Title from indicia: Master of Kung Fu, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: The Hands of Shang-Chi, Master of Kung Fu
  - Contents of Box 266: (Box 266)
    - Title from indicia: Master of Kung Fu, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
      - Cover Title: The Hands of Shang-Chi, Master of Kung Fu
    - Title from indicia: Moon Knight, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Red Sonja, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Rom, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
  - Contents of Box 267: (Box 267)
    - Title from indicia: Rom, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Special Marvel Edition, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Special Marvel Edition featuring The Hands of Shang-Chi, Master of Kung Fu
    - Title from indicia: Star Wars, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
    - Title from indicia: Super Villain Team-Up, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
      Note: This comic series contains a new cover title on each issue which consists of two Marvel villians. Cover titles not listed here.
    - Title from indicia: Tower of Shadows, Issues from: 1960s,1970s
    - Title from indicia: Warlock, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Worlds Unknown, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Worlds Unknown presents The Thing Called... Killdozer
      - Cover Title: Worlds Unknown presents The Golden Voyage of Sinbad
  - Contents of Box 268: (Box 268)
    - Title from indicia: Alpha Flight, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Amazing Spider-Man, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Amazing Spider-Man Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Annie, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Avengers, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Blade Runner, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Captain America, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
    - Title from indicia: Cloak and Dagger, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Conan the Barbarian, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Conan the Barbarian Movie Special, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Contest of Champions, Issues from: 1980s
  - Contents of Box 269: (Box 269)
    - Title from indicia: Daredevil, Issues from: 1960s,1970s,1980s
      - Cover Title: Daredevil: The Man Without Fear
      - Cover Title: Daredevil and Black Widow
    - Title from indicia: The Dark Crystal, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Defenders, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: The New Defenders
    - Title from indicia: Dennis the Menace, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Devil Dinosaur, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Doctor Strange, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Doctor Who, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Dragonslayer, Issues from: 1980s
  - Contents of Box 270: (Box 270)
    - Title from indicia: The Eternals, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Fantastic Four, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Fantastic Four Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Ghost Rider, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Ghost Rider, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
    - Title from indicia: G. I. Joe, A Real American Hero, Issues from: 1980s
  - Contents of Box 271: (Box 271)
    - Title from indicia: Godzilla, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Hercules, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Howard the Duck, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Incredible Hulk, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Iron Man, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: James Bond, For Your Eyes Only, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Krull, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Kull the Conqueror, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Last Star Fighter, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Team-Up, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Marvel Two-in-One, Issues from: 1970s